

Adrianov Pavel

Male, 31 year, born on 11 August 1987

pavel@adrianov.pro — preferred means of communication

Skype: adrianovpavel

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pavel-adrianov/

Another site: http://adrianov.pro

Reside in: Simferopol

Citizenship: Ukraine, work permit at: Russia, Ukraine

Ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

Data Scientist. Python developer.

3 500

USD

IT, Internet, Telecom

- Software Development
- Networks
- Project Management

Employment: project work, part time, full time

Work schedule: remote working, flexible schedule, full day, shift schedule

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 12 years 3 months

August 2015 — till now

3 years 4 months

TireConnect

Ukraine

Software developer. Data scientist.

Develop and support huge e-commerce project.

January 2013 — January 2015 2 years 1 month

TeamAve

Simferopol

PHP developer

Working on a large ecommerce project. Was involved in the integration of payment systems, scaling the project, optimizing for high loads.

December 2011 — December 2013 2 years 1 month

ameria GmbH

Simferopol, ameria.de

PHP developer. Team Lead.

Was engaged in the development of large projects on Symfony2.

June 2009 — November 2011 2 years 6 months

NewVision

Simferopol

PHP developer

The work was carried out over several high-load projects with large volumes of data (Exchange of links, Multithreaded indexing of third-party web-sites, processing of large amounts of data).

April 2008 — September 2009 1 year 6 months

depositfiles.com

Kyiv, depositfiles.com

PHP developer

The responsibility was to optimize databases for high loads (postgresql, mysql), code optimization, load distribution on servers, setting up nginx, redis.

November 2007 — March 2008 5 months

skidki-ua.com

Kyiv, skidki-ua.com

Team leader

Lead developer of the project skidki-ua.com. The project developed by me on symfony 1.4.

January 2006 — August 2007 1 year 8 months

Freelance

PHP developer

Worked as a freelancer. Carried out orders for various CMS (RunCMS, Joomla, Typo3, WordPress, etc)

Education

Higher

2009

Vernadsky Taurida National University, Simferopol

Faculty of Mathematics, Apply Math

Key skills

Languages

Russian — native

English — I can attend an interview Ukrainian — I am a fluent speaker

Skills

Machine Leaning Big Data Data Analysis Python Symfony Nginx PHP MongoDB

Further information

About me

Senior software developer with 12 year of solid experience in IT. My main passion for now is machine learning and data science. Also I have a lot of experience in PHP and Python development. Looking for product manager, team leader, data-scientist position. I am familar with machine learning algorithms and python libraries such as Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-learn, XGBoost, etc. Also I have a lot of experience with PHP frameworks such as Symfony and Laravel. I have build several highload and big data projects.

Design Patterns

Redis

Checkout my accomplishments and certificates:

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/7YVTA6XT5Z9H - Machine Learning and Data Science Specialization.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/3MCLDSDVCQRY - Introduction to Machine Learning.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/TAP4VKTPCLP8 - Big Data Analysis: Hive, Spark SQL, DataFrames and GraphFrames.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/W59WWG5P47VF - Big Data Essentials: HDFS, MapReduce and Spark RDD.

One of my hobby is creating devices on arduino or raspberry. For example: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CHe23H-Dpm4

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6osE_LyXUqc

I'm fond of rock music, fantastic literature and mountain skiing.

You can contact with me via email for hiring or any other questions.